izanau.com 2019-04-10

# Privacy Policy | Izanau

Our highest priority at Active Gaming Media Inc. (hereinafter referred to as "our company") is to protect any user's personal information. To help guarantee safe communication between those seeking employment and Japanese companies,  the community site IZANAU (hereinafter referred to as "this site") has established the following policy on the protection of personal information. Before registering and using this site, users are required to read and agree to this Privacy policy. This Privacy Policy is subject to change. It is advised that you review this Privacy Policy for changes periodically.

 **1\. Management of Personal Information**

Our company collects the accurate and up-to-date personal information of users who voluntarily provide this information. Through continued employee training, our company conducts security system maintenance to prevent any unauthorized access to, loss, damage, falsification, leakage, etc. of personal information. Additional safety measures will be implemented when necessary.

 **2\. Personal Information**

The contents of this site are public. However, in order to use this site,  users must register the following items of personal information:During Account Creation:  
· Full Name  
· Valid Email Address  
· Password

Additionally, to apply for jobs and/or contact companies, the user must register the following items of personal information:  
*Registered profiles are open to the public.

During Profile Creation:  
· Name  
· Birthday  
· Country of Citizenship  
· Country of Residence  
· Visa Availability  
· Languages Proficiency  
· Academic Background  
· Work Experience  
· Skills  
· Hobbies (if any)

When you apply for jobs, the company will be able to view the following personal information listed below.

・E-mail address  

 **3\. Other Sources of Information**  

To improve the quality of this site and site navigation by its users, our company may also collect the following types of information:  
· Logfiles  
· Cookies  
· Web Beacons

 **4\. Usage and Handling of Personal Information**

Personal information from each registered user may be used for the following purposes:· Statistical Surveys· To make profile update requests to the user  
· Newsletters about this site  
· In order to contact the user about new job information

 **5\. Disclosure of Personal Information to Third Party Companies**

Our company will not disclose your personal information to any third parties unless:  
· The user’s expressed consent is received  
· Authorities based on laws and ordinances, require us to do so

 **6\. Safety Measures**

In order to ensure the accuracy and safety of personal information, thorough safety measures are in place.

 **7\. Personal Information Management**

Personal information can be edited or deleted at any time by the user.If support regarding the management of personal information is required, please contact this site’s management through the[ Contact Us form](https://izanau.com/contact).

 **8\. Changes to this Privacy Policy**

This site reserves the right to update this Privacy Policy without prior notice. Continued use of this site will be regarded as the user's consent to any changes in this Privacy Policy.
